Register of the Zhongguo Guo Min Dang Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive (Zong Cai), 1912-1987
  Correspondence, memoranda, telegrams, speeches, publications, photographs, and other records of Chiang Kai-shek. In addition to Hoover's online database, a published index is available at Stanford's East Asia Library.
  總裁檔案
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 101, 1949 (Reels 1-5)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 102, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 103, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 104, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 105, 1949 (Reels 1-6)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 106, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 107, 1949 (Reels 1-2)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 110.1, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 120, 1949 (Reels 1-2, 2A, 2B, 3-11, 11A, 12-13)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 130, 1949 (Reels 1-24)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 130.1, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 131, 1949 (Reels 1-3)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 132, 1949 (Reels 1-8, 8A, 9-42)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 133, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 134, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 135, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 136, 1949 (Reels 1-2)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 137, 1949 (Reels 1, 1A)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 138, 1949 (Reels 1-4)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 139, 1949 (Reels 1-3)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 140, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 141, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 150, 1949 (Reels 1-2)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 160, 1949 (Reels 1-10, 10A)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 170, 1949 (Reels 1-6, 6A, 7-15)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 180, 1949 (Reels 1, 1A, 2-5, 5A, 6-11)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 185, 1949 (Reels 1-15, 15A, 16-20)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 185.1, 1949 (Reel 1)
  - Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek Archive 185.2, 1949 (Reel 1)